<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="units">
        <item>Imperial</item>
        <item>Metric</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="arnold_quotes">
        <item>It\'s simple, if it jiggles, it\'s fat.</item>
        <item>The mind is the limit. As long as the mind can envision the fact that you can do something, you can do it, as long as you really believe 100 percent.</item>
        <item>The worst thing I can be is the same as everybody else. I hate that.</item>
        <item>Failure is not an option. Everyone has to succeed.</item>
        <item>As long as I live, I will never forget that day 21 years ago when I raised my hand and took the oath of citizenship. Do you know how proud I was? I was so proud that I walked around with an American flag around my shoulders all day long.</item>
        <item>Start wide, expand further, and never look back.</item>
        <item>Training gives us an outlet for suppressed energies created by stress and thus tones the spirit just as exercise conditions the body.</item>
        <item>For me life is continuously being hungry. The meaning of life is not simply to exist, to survive, but to move ahead, to go up, to achieve, to conquer.</item>
        <item>Help others and give something back. I guarantee you will discover that while public service improves the lives and the world around you, its greatest reward is the enrichment and new meaning it will bring your own life.</item>
        <item>The resistance that you fight physically in the gym and the resistance that you fight in life can only build a strong character.</item>
        <item>Bodybuilding is much like any other sport. To be successful, you must dedicate yourself 100% to your training, diet and mental approach.</item>
        <item>My body is like breakfast, lunch, and dinner. I don\'t think about it, I just have it.</item>
        <item>The last three or four reps is what makes the muscle grow. This area of pain divides the champion from someone else who is not a champion. That\'s what most people lack, having the guts to go on and just say they\'ll go through the pain no matter what happens.</item>
        <item>If it\'s hard to remember, it\'ll be difficult to forget.</item>
        <item>What we face may look insurmountable. But I learned something from all those years of training and competing. I learned something from all those sets and reps when I didn\'t think I could lift another ounce of weight. What I learned is that we are always stronger than we know.</item>
        <item>\'I\'ll be back\' always sounded a little girly to me.</item>
        <item>Learned helplessness is the giving-up reaction, the quitting response that follows from the belief that whatever you do doesn\'t matter.</item>
        <item>I welcome and seek your ideas, but do not bring me small ideas; bring me big ideas to match our future.</item>
        <item>I knew I was a winner back in the late sixties. I knew I was destined for great things. People will say that kind of thinking is totally immodest. I agree. Modesty is not a word that applies to me in any way - I hope it never will.</item>
        <item>I do the same exercises I did 50 years ago and they still work. I eat the same food I ate 50 years ago and it still works.</item>
        <item>I\'m addicted to exercising and I have to do something every day.</item>
        <item>I just use my muscles as a conversation piece, like someone walking a cheetah down 42nd Street.</item>
        <item>I don\'t suffer of anything that I\'ve lost.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>